{
    "subject": "resource/The_Fire_Brigade",
    "predicate": "property/distributor",
    "object": "resource/Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer",
    "human_readable": "The Fire Brigade was distributed by Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.987008273601532,
            "question": "Is 'The Fire Brigade' a film produced by Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9618038535118103,
            "question": "Besides 'The Fire Brigade', what other movies might Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer have distributed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8191633820533752,
            "question": "Which company was responsible for distributing 'The Fire Brigade'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7406585216522217,
            "question": "Who distributed the movie 'The Fire Brigade'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6846392750740051,
            "question": "Name a movie distributed by Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6740020513534546,
            "question": "Was Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer involved in distributing any films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5756159424781799,
            "question": "What was the name of the studio that released 'The Fire Brigade'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4899047613143921,
            "question": "What is the name of the studio that released 'The Fire Brigade'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48907455801963806,
            "question": "What type of organization is Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3279726803302765,
            "question": "Is 'The Fire Brigade' a well-known film?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Fire Brigade was distributed by Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3737_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of organization is Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3737_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the studio that released 'The Fire Brigade'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3737_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of the studio that released 'The Fire Brigade'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3737_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3737_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3737_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3737_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3737_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3737_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3737_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3737_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3737_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3737_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3737_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because according to document `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3737/re-ranker-msmarco/45.txt`, The Fire Brigade was indeed distributed by Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer Distributing Corporation."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information from the document `dbpedia_3737/re-ranker-msmarco/45.txt` supports that \"The Fire Brigade\" was distributed by Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer, as it states \"Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer Pictures Corporation production; distributed by Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer Distributing Corporation.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}